Speaker 1: The Washington Uniparty just crapped out a border deal that, as you would expect, puts America last.
Speaker 1: The deal trades more money for Ukraine and Israel in return for keeping our borders wide open
Speaker 1: and actually giving 1.5 million illegal border crossers amnesty while locking in green card giveaways through 2030,
Speaker 1: presumably in the expectation that they will become loyal socialist voters as previous waves of illegals have.
Speaker 1: The welfare warfare state in full effect with the added bonus of replacing Americans with a crop of brand new voters.
Speaker 1: If it worked for California, by gum, it can work for America.
Speaker 1: This little deuce was hatched by a handful of corrupt rhinos teaming up with socialist Democrats.
Speaker 1: As always, when you hear the word bipartisan in Washington, that means the corrupt Uniparty is coming for you.
Speaker 1: First, the specifics. It would spend $118 billion.
Speaker 1: For this, we would get legalization of 1.5 million illegals per year. That's $5,000 per day.
Speaker 1: The other $10 million plus illegals will presumably have to wait for another war, perhaps the one we are cooking up with Iran or over Taiwan.
Speaker 1: It hands $2.3 billion immediately to the non-government organizations that are making a mint importing welfare cases to every nook and cranny of America
Speaker 1: because Democrats do know who brought them to the party.
Speaker 1: And then comes the payoff to Republicans.
Speaker 1: The bill plows over $93 billion into our rapidly expanding universe of wars, including $14 billion to Israel and another $5 billion for Hamas, or Gaza.
Speaker 1: Incidentally, just last week, Rand Paul was marveling how we somehow managed to fund both sides of wars.
Speaker 1: So there you go.
Speaker 1: Beyond Hamas, the sellout leads no war behind, with $5 billion going to gin up a war with China.
Speaker 1: They're already moving weapons to Australia in preparation.
Speaker 1: And $2.3 billion for the Red Sea, which is used by European and Chinese ships, but not by American ships.
Speaker 1: Somehow, though, we must pay.
Speaker 1: Finally, a crisp $60 billion for Ukraine's lost cause,
Speaker 1: so Zelensky can continue sending the flower of Ukraine's youth to die in his pointless meat-grander.
Speaker 1: Of course, the left is still angry because having intentionally thrown open the southern border to human traffic,
Speaker 1: 10 million political footballs, they wanted more amnesty so they could flip more states blue.
Speaker 1: Meanwhile, Republican voters, of course, once again feel betrayed by a party that will sell them down the river
Speaker 1: if it funds just one corrupt dictator and secures some cheap fruit pickers and manual labor for their corporate donors.
Speaker 1: So what's next?
Speaker 1: Brought to you by Unchained.com.
Speaker 1: Joe Biden could fix immigration immediately with the stroke of a pen by simply reinstating Trump-era policies,
Speaker 1: including the so-called Remain in Mexico policy that required amnesty applicants to stay put until processed.
Speaker 1: Instead, his handlers are trying to milk their crisis to replace the current voters with a brand-new crop,
Speaker 1: all while funding the army of non-government organizations that sustain their activist industrial complex.
Speaker 1: All with a GOP too corrupt to care so long as the donor checks keep flowing.
Speaker 1: Whether the Uniparty passes this turd sandwich or keeps kicking the can down the open border road,
Speaker 1: it's going to benefit Donald Trump in November.
Speaker 1: At which point, all eyes turn to the margin of cheating to know whether there is light in that tunnel
Speaker 1: or whether we've got even darker days ahead.
Speaker 1: Okay, we'll be watching.
Speaker 1: See you next time.